ip-address.org 2017-08-07

# IP Address - Disclaimer Privacy Policy

At IP-Address.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [IP-Address.org](http://www.ip-address.org/)

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit IP-Address.org, and how we safeguard your information.   
We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

### IP-Address.org and Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers, we collect and use the data contained in log files. 

The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, referring/exit pages, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### IP-Address.org, Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. IP-Address.org don't use cookies by itself but our third party partners: Google Analytics, AdSense, Facebook use cookie as well for tracking the activity and advertising purposes. We do not have control over their cookie/ 

### Third party advertisements

We also use third party advertisements IP-Address.org to support our site. 

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. 

This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

### Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses DART cookies to serve ads on IP-Address.org. 

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. 

DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. 

To find out how Google use cookies check out [Google cookies](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/)

You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html)

You can opt out Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### IP Address News

We are very glad to present you IP-Address.org Most powerful IP tracer and IP tracker tool on the Web. 

The idea behind our site is to give you all available IP tools for free which will help you to find out anything what you need to know about owner of any IP address or domain. 

### IP Location Finder

The site is still in development and the new IP finder modules will be added to our project in future.   
Right now you can use any of IP finder modules below: 

### IP Checker

My IP location tracing module below which check IP from your visitors and show IP information's to them is free for use.   
We require only to leave credit to our site intact. If you remove credit to us we will block you from using IP location module. 

My IP Location Tracking Module for your site 

### My IP Location Tracer

To add My IP location tracer module to your site copy script below and place where you would like to appear on your website.
